{"creationDate":"2018-04-30 14:12:20","type":"questionnaire","id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3","title":"Palavras importantes ","questions":[{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_rjrq8j77p8jgqqzg2m","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"aguentar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"z35jjfqwdljgqqzg2m","answer":"supporter","detail":"une douleur...","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_ukwkuccq0chjgqqsvmk","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"secar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"tbsttdueh6ljgqqsvmk","answer":"sécher","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_tmewkplqeljgqqrxif","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"assar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"o3thlv2s69jgqqrxif","answer":"rôtir","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_e2c4h5ion0gjgqqfwzb","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"conferer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"37emuude5b3jgqqfwzb","answer":"coïncider","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"qxi4pnivqanjgqqgrxg","answer":"vérifier","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_lyifw8um33mjgqqey31","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"soar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"8tm9f4afcfjgqqey31","answer":"sonner","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_cb18x0mh36fjgqqdef8","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"estacionar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"41mnhnioubljgqqdef9","answer":"stationner","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_93azz422ooajgnykpel","questionLabel":"Palavra","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"aquecimento","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"xh5e097ip3ajgnykpel","answer":"chauffage","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_r6duetcg6ejjgnyb1ge","questionLabel":"Verbo","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"empourrar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"adp29q1jfq4jgnyb1ge","answer":"pousser","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_npjsd39i2yjgnxzrv2","questionLabel":"Verbo","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"frear","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"b3dxz6fti9ijgnxzrv2","answer":"freiner","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_1t0emybdh5mjgmnx5ow","questionLabel":"Palavra","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"seguro","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bu2jkd31ncrjgmnx5ox","answer":"sûr","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_h2wb4bgslljgmglizb","questionLabel":"Palavra","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"cedo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"zw4ysm81hipjgmglizb","answer":"tôt","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_xp5rhyk0f0rjgmg1wnl","questionLabel":"Verbo","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"negar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"3y8er2jz4ddjgmg1wnl","answer":"refuser","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"adqjiztixo8jgmg25y1","answer":"nier","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_degujctrhsnjgmfh5q1","questionLabel":"Verbo","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"mostrar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"qu37e6f67zjgmfh5q2","answer":"montrer","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3_y5fwqzwmqbpjgmel5ia","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"estar com pressa","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"tewbblvngdjgmel5ia","answer":"être pressé","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"m58f7p8mfjjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Verbo","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"abranger","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ps0phj9jcfejgmbp5i3","answer":"couvrir","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"42pi91tb84ejgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"recém","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"4n5crx4yzqejgmbp5i3","answer":"récemment","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"95p2vspr565jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pior","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"v0l5paplc3ajgmbp5i3","answer":"pire","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"egusmvhj6ujgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"atrás","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"phzl16digbjgmbp5i3","answer":"derrière","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"zz3i1ivl3hjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"portão","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"76ohjeq51anjgmbp5i3","answer":"portail","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"lcvetosm2qbjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"descansar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"2aubf3d9d7xjgmbp5i3","answer":"se reposer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"whkg9x35x08jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"cruzar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"nlro9jy519jjgmbp5i3","answer":"croiser","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"wrayunw62zjjgmbp5i3","answer":"traverser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ei613ilgfk5jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"gastar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"y5463goumgnjgmbp5i3","answer":"dépenser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"dud7fkdh65ijgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pertencer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"7deghuv8pthjgmbp5i3","answer":"appartenir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"5fa8illgqvojgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"atuar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"453j5mf0nl8jgmbp5i3","answer":"agir","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"bzyrbybzu8jgmbp5i3","answer":"jouer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"blmf9cvoiikjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"levantar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"7ray1pl7tjojgmbp5i3","answer":"élever","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"cpa9b825ptnjgmbp5i3","answer":"lever","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"k64gfp8a6bjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"merecer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"f9i1en7h6ihjgmbp5i3","answer":"mériter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"o10kd225d9ajgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pular","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"0h5iwlgavy2ojgmbp5i3","answer":"sauter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"gtefpl0duqjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"sustentar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"z37xzmfvcipjgmbp5i3","answer":"soutenir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"zpf5mvz0dejgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"odiar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"vdvhzyl73ljgmbp5i3","answer":"détester","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"h4k4rr50e5ljgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"mãe","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"9h1h63cxltvjgmbp5i3","answer":"mère","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"mufonbi27nhjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"initiar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"lmld50sb5amjgmbp5i3","answer":"commencer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9e9ic99qwqjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"exigir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"zp50ra8ijugjgmbp5i3","answer":"exiger","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"62skxkrm5mhjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"derrotar","detail":"(jeux)","answers":[{"id":"sq8tertfv8fjgmbp5i3","answer":"battre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"k234mqbnywjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"recusar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ze5m7v8sajjgmbp5i3","answer":"refuser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"s8jkn0eebsjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"duvidar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"gq90248ll5ajgmbp5i3","answer":"douter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"kmv79lxoy3jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"misturar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"elq4qndxotrjgmbp5i3","answer":"mélanger","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"3zctwped26cjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"emprego","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"rq3cds557wdjgmbp5i3","answer":"emploi","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":false},{"id":"xwounbddsojgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"sacada","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"36h6yv1ep7ljgmbp5i3","answer":"balcon","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"5lkhmz3y9aijgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"conseguir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"07t5ls7e58zwjgmbp5i3","answer":"réussir","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"56smzgywykwjgmbp5i3","answer":"arriver","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"hc31idpq1xgjgmbp5i3","answer":"obtenir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"foundType":"question","questionnaireTitle":"Palavras importantes ","questionnaireId":"di3ybmd51d8jgc7thdt","favorite":true},{"id":"2qdhuj86wf4jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"falar em","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"02b2uvo5or3zjgmbp5i3","answer":"parler de","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"rmefkofnhqjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"perigoso","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"9xeuqb8gj3fjgmbp5i3","answer":"dangereux","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"wlje8atg69rjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pesar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"5d6n87p0wnajgmbp5i3","answer":"peser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"gqxvdm3fq8cjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"algodão","detail":" ","answers":[{"id":"2j8ktdgko7fjgmbp5i3","answer":"coton","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"4d5ymubvr3hjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"chumbir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"l7j8drmjdspjgmbp5i3","answer":"couler","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"mal7dznfm1jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"outro","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ewyrgx6e7nhjgmbp5i3","answer":"autre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"dmqlfuojz9jjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"garota","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"djuul0o9txjgmbp5i3","answer":"fille","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"x80x0tsf99jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"resposa","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"93nvhjgoud4jgmbp5i3","answer":"réponse","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"rcr1900ko7ajgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"varias","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"p7872zs6z2jgmbp5i3","answer":"plusieurs","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"d9cng8jf9k9jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"qualquer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"8iymkz0e18ijgmbp5i3","answer":"quelconque","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"hlepqp07f2mjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"nenhuma","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"u0s9pesj4ojgmbp5i3","answer":"aucune","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"enf2czbrznjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"escolha","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"oakj7cmzwljgmbp5i3","answer":"choix","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"luso1czybwjjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"algumas","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"qqot86m4xmjgmbp5i3","answer":"quelques","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"tvu3ud6bg1sjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"dobro","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"xw9ltruc4fkjgmbp5i3","answer":"double","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"m3ov6qyre8jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"seculo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"4g4zn7yxtysjgmbp5i3","answer":"siècle","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"cvyoh1j85hnjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"vó","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"qlw8vtusi4jjgmbp5i3","answer":"grand mère","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"d2fon2x5zsrjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"avó","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"rszytdjnmjejgmbp5i3","answer":"grand père","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9e0ai8izaqbjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"maioria","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"6yqj2i82vgbjgmbp5i3","answer":"majorité","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"wb5xrfgllnjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"sétima, sétimo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"451ek8tbksbjgmbp5i3","answer":"septième","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"b7w50gs81vjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"nova, nono","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"n69cc6fxy1fjgmbp5i3","answer":"neuvième","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"bnlsqzfc9avjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"neto, neta","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"r2fqq5oqxtjgmbp5i3","answer":"petite fille, petit fils","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1v9wt9zvokojgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"oitavo, oitava","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"b92tiq97iqujgmbp5i3","answer":"huitième","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"qvfsfpnckcjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"tonelada","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"gbvmij6g1vjgmbp5i3","answer":"tonne","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"nymoidy8rbjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"metade","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"dz1eit4ije5jgmbp5i3","answer":"moitié","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"lfph07idewjjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"par","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"gql8o6fte68jgmbp5i3","answer":"paire","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"x32o0eciahdjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"fanzendeiro","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"xjbh2j2810djgmbp5i3","answer":"fermier","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"3n06ayv8vmjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"brinquedo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"928cfg47waajgmbp5i3","answer":"jouet","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"x14k4bpjgvjjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"amargo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"lsfc206cw4ojgmbp5i3","answer":"amer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"u12ubdwe3majgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"apesar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"qghikwtf42cjgmbp5i3","answer":"malgré","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"wg56b7um8ipjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"areia","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ynaal2n297jgmbp5i3","answer":"sable","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"a4b82x6m2kvjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"as vezes","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"hlxu2slb24kjgmbp5i3","answer":"parfois","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"foundType":"question","questionnaireTitle":"Palavras importantes ","showAnwsers":true,"favorite":true},{"id":"7bimzjzeyf4jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"barriga","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"3a3pibpt0ctjgmbp5i3","answer":"ventre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"isw6pk5ol4jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"bastante","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"kokw52k75cmjgmbp5i3","answer":"assez","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"i4w9xmw4tsjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"beijo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"751g707m5aojgmbp5i3","answer":"bise","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"k43o0n8nqrjgmbp5i3","answer":"bisou","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"kqg43f0rjujgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"boate","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"rudu2a8eyzjgmbp5i3","answer":"boite","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"2jvntrzoyz3jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"braço","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bl4mqg805pbjgmbp5i3","answer":"bras","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"bz1etd6zzrujgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"calças","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"p7myqv9bluijgmbp5i3","answer":"pantalon","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"08wmzsbd0xoujgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"carruagem","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"eayspw9ariwjgmbp5i3","answer":"wagon","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"fhc6pgtxfcjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"codigo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"un8wwwg9r0jjgmbp5i3","answer":"code","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ze60fco5kojgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"comprido","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"goo5yeagbsojgmbp5i3","answer":"long","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"wge9tmv424bjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"concha","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"o3uelwnd7ajgmbp5i3","answer":"coquillage","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"375la6o5alhjgmbp5i3","answer":"coquille","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"6jjyylvpjdfjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"corrente","detail":"métal","answers":[{"id":"2aeeg368w8fjgmbp5i3","answer":"courant","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"y3oj5advq9ljgmbp5i3","answer":"chaine","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"y17mowqz9sjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"doente","detail":"estar doente","answers":[{"id":"i3o3gofisukjgmbp5i3","answer":"malade","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"foundType":"question","questionnaireTitle":"Palavras importantes "},{"id":"6aliwa6v13bjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"dono","detail":"A dona é uma vilha mulher","answers":[{"id":"ocasb5lyf2cjgmbp5i3","answer":"propriétaire","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"6mwh5a8ioyfjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"dor","detail":"Tenho dores de cabeça","answers":[{"id":"ajxzub2weoijgmbp5i3","answer":"douleur","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"favorite":true},{"id":"712pj8u2bw9jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"então","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"mwozfgwu78gjgmbp5i3","answer":"alors","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"yiqmgjetqejgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"escada","detail":"Eu não gusto de escadas rollantes","answers":[{"id":"m57j2inppxjgmbp5i3","answer":"escalier","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"e52tdsq11yljgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"escova","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"per3ay40axjgmbp5i3","answer":"brosse","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1lhh6aetq2zjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"espelho","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"a735rkptj5jgmbp5i3","answer":"miroir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"gguy1ifk3wujgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"esquina","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"xqc4kl2qw3jgmbp5i3","answer":"coin","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"eb2wgz6oi0ojgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"ferramentas","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"w11lw5ux2zljgmbp5i3","answer":"outils","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"mbkhmlno5yjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"folha","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"8jed8j5l53pjgmbp5i3","answer":"feuille","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"lj0f936g3fjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"fome","detail":"Estou com fome","answers":[{"id":"5xe1i0730nwjgmbp5i3","answer":"faim","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"uo7ap4ovb0djgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"geladeria","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"681az90id4njgmbp5i3","answer":"frigo","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"tq2eg5h4utnjgmbp5i3","answer":"frigidaire","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"asp0ulmo37ujgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"guarda-chuva","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"sdo1gv2bx8fjgmbp5i3","answer":"parapluie","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"7k8j4uxwpuajgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"inicio","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"oade59l90kdjgmbp5i3","answer":"début","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9npme14b5qjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"jolho","detail":"Meus pernas e jolhos estam dolorosos","answers":[{"id":"fsyuls11g2jgmbp5i3","answer":"genou","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"94if7bvtnemjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"juiz","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"54g9nlbign7jgmbp5i3","answer":"juge","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"4hj6yxnyu7ljgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"junto","detail":"ou junta","answers":[{"id":"devbwfhiuamjgmbp5i3","answer":"ensemble","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"0lz362nv8a3kjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"lã","detail":"Eu não gusto de pele, prefriero lã","answers":[{"id":"dsgoqq98d5qjgmbp5i3","answer":"laine","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"cx8zo2fejcgjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"lar","detail":"maison","answers":[{"id":"gpzk1pi5p7jgmbp5i3","answer":"foyer","correctDistance":0,"point":1,"detail":""},{"id":"waghtgapu5jgmbp5i3","answer":"maison","detail":"au sens du foyer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"89nhjrgj0f8jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"livraria","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"5fytorqk3f5jgmbp5i3","answer":"librairie","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"5otpu9aykjhjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"logo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"oe8497oa1ahjgmbp5i3","answer":"ensuite","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"xvjcx0glinljgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"longe","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"4twg7vpc7ijgmbp5i3","answer":"loin","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"f5qzh856d4jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"luva","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"2194f3tsguajgmbp5i3","answer":"gant","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"fezr420xhu9jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"marco","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"tigrf7y6pqijgmbp5i3","answer":"marque","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"wede0qw8k2fjgmbp5i3","answer":"étape","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"g9y0d85wi4cjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"massà","detail":"italiennes","answers":[{"id":"anlfe24394jgmbp5i3","answer":"pâtes","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"questionnaireTitle":"Palavras importantes ","questionnaireId":"di3ybmd51d8jgc7thdt","questionnaireType":"questionnaire","foundType":"answer"},{"id":"a0c582crta9jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"meia","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"nl435509mxjgmbp5i3","answer":"chaussette","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"82czyjjcyuxjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"moeda","detail":"monnaie","answers":[{"id":"xknsln18bpfjgmbp5i3","answer":"pièce","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"j6vhqe28sihjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"nariz","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ilk3cldhxdajgmbp5i3","answer":"nez","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"k1pgga3qifqjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"nota","detail":"argent","answers":[{"id":"pmp9mkpg1c9jgmbp5i3","answer":"billet","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ycf1kegb6cijgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"nunca","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"265u0jn40wvjgmbp5i3","answer":"jamais","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"pkhd63jzduqjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"oculos","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"phdzk4h0rjijgmbp5i3","answer":"lunettes","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"qutol41bucjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"oléo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ruolll18ivjgmbp5i3","answer":"huile","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"gpj9e3sy7ypjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"olho","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"31scv0ww59ejgmbp5i3","answer":"oeuil","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9a7flleq0ebjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"ouro","detail":"métal","answers":[{"id":"z8r942zv7nejgmbp5i3","answer":"or","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"3ob1igh8jc3jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"padaria","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"o6ogxntx7bjgmbp5i3","answer":"boulangerie","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"wbi9kbql46jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"parabéns","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"dpjztozd8rtjgmbp5i3","answer":"félicitations","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"8wuhzgduirgjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"parraro","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"t3lcwom0ibjgmbp5i3","answer":"oiseau","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ka4bfmybc9jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"peça","detail":"de moteur","answers":[{"id":"2bxj59he82qjgmbp5i3","answer":"pièce","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"h8gmxh5uk19jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pedaço","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"jun1jh77zaqjgmbp5i3","answer":"morceau","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"4i4jkun4jgbjgmbp5i3","answer":"bout","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"bts7tvriqjijgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pele","detail":"cuir","answers":[{"id":"iabqi3j7jkjgmbp5i3","answer":"peau","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"koiq7i1rzibjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pelo menos","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ynu5dgw1br8jgmbp5i3","answer":"au moins","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"taqv8m3nfsjjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pente","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"r8zzcf24otjgmbp5i3","answer":"peigne","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"195fibjcpqxjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"perna","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"nhwg5h8sgtjgmbp5i3","answer":"jambe","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"vwzztj2yljjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"perto","detail":"proche","answers":[{"id":"0ewf18p19h9ujgmbp5i3","answer":"près","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1gn8ks2ydyqjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pilha","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"pq5a8nb67cljgmbp5i3","answer":"pile","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"b2e9tl9sw6njgmbp5i3","answer":"batterie","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1molgg7lhzhijgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"povo","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"2bxi1b28l9xjgmbp5i3","answer":"peuple","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"27k1ap56kuvjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"prata","detail":"métal","answers":[{"id":"9n3sbgu99qljgmbp5i3","answer":"argent","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"o93vcqrbduljgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"present ","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"yioazh73w3ljgmbp5i3","answer":"cadeau","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"2idriznkqfgjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"projeto","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"sqfctzt4gwjgmbp5i3","answer":"projet","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"3tpoq0ihhcjjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"quadrada","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"gpmxr38mms4jgmbp5i3","answer":"carrée","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jaanv2wvcmojgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"refeição","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"0h7bymlq71htjgmbp5i3","answer":"repas","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"rtt6bgynazjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"revista","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"d64mq4rw59jgmbp5i3","answer":"magazine","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"7zwrmcoo2uojgmbp5i3","answer":"revue","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"l06fgvryfkjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"vestido","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"4p1l52tteuxjgmbp5i3","answer":"robe","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"vu971gtq7zqjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"roda","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"vh7tvoyezmqjgmbp5i3","answer":"roue","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"h8kfenuc2ohjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"rosto","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"fc9uibatoxjgmbp5i3","answer":"visage","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"pafygsktjvojgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"roupa","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"y3zmq8d6cphjgmbp5i3","answer":"vêtement","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"q3i80fapfdqjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"saia","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"5tyxndslauwjgmbp5i3","answer":"jupe","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"t1iddrj3m6jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"seda","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"24ta6be0sgyjgmbp5i3","answer":"soie","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jlrl3qopzmdjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"sede","detail":"Estou com sede","answers":[{"id":"vm05xhvq8xjgmbp5i3","answer":"soif","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"3vn862j97gojgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"sobrenome","detail":"de famille","answers":[{"id":"jurjaws3sujgmbp5i3","answer":"nom","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"y6c3ikmehcjgmbp5i3","answer":"nom de famille","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"lrjniju52icjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"sombra","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"s54snfs9ugijgmbp5i3","answer":"ombre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"cu9bxq0p1bojgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"teclado","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"xdqrekz1fajgmbp5i3","answer":"clavier","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"gh4ofuyz11cjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"tela","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"8llk0nhisljjgmbp5i3","answer":"écran","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"29477q6emgujgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"toalha","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"rwzjtrqpixjgmbp5i3","answer":"serviette","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"k848vsugexkjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"velha","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"p9uoyfcxq5jgmbp5i3","answer":"vieille","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"o4vyjslyjtjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"gente","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ef5p5ks896wjgmbp5i3","answer":"gens","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"3lsx92x1i22jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"cidadão","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"y371o72i23sjgmbp5i3","answer":"citoyen","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1uthtso6xnfjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"casal","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ckdw0qyehirjgmbp5i3","answer":"couple","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9x1t2oh3w2ajgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"preso","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"sowtygozv0kjgmbp5i3","answer":"prisonnier","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"gp3q9grkfeljgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"sujeito","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ned0jw3y4vjgmbp5i3","answer":"sujet","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ubyhocwl85mjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"socia","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"tkom1s4qukjgmbp5i3","answer":"associé","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"fje60qoppmsjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"garoto","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"h7tevobct2vjgmbp5i3","answer":"garçon","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"foundType":"question","questionnaireTitle":"Palavras importantes ","questionnaireId":"di3ybmd51d8jgc7thdt","questionnaireType":"questionnaire"},{"id":"e6nmk27bi3jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"gênero","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"n8m2xy7ivbjgmbp5i3","answer":"genre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"buo3n2v3vnpjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"multidão","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"fqn8mm117q8jgmbp5i3","answer":"foule","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ytsl9ys7gekjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"hospedes","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"2tsdhx551vojgmbp5i3","answer":"invités","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9xpn21frhsnjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"abrir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"l066jn9mmbjgmbp5i3","answer":"ouvrir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"vo0lb0019wjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"acabar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"i8l4szpcaddjgmbp5i3","answer":"finir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"3o9p1llt8sjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"aceitar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ddf21qfqlnjgmbp5i3","answer":"accepter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"4s4j0bg1h68jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"acender","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"u3rxfl0uyuejgmbp5i3","answer":"allumer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"waybyfxnckjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"achar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"z1mzgav1jujgmbp5i3","answer":"penser","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"ojc3gzkpxvmjgmbp5i3","answer":"trouver","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"2t91xds51xsjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"acontecer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"qpiysdh47rdjgmbp5i3","answer":"se produire","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"yacq17jmpjajgmbp5i3","answer":"se passer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"c0zz3k8woopjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"acordar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"hxlopr36gnljgmbp5i3","answer":"se réveiller","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"7919jxfdvm8jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"adorar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"yuy2mze7sajgmbp5i3","answer":"adorer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"wf3yjxraf8jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"agradecer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"znlcoir2ta8jgmbp5i3","answer":"remercier","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"foundType":"question","questionnaireTitle":"Palavras importantes ","questionnaireId":"di3ybmd51d8jgc7thdt","questionnaireType":"questionnaire"},{"id":"x8jr9qek3wjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"ajudar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"nowxzem0qfqjgmbp5i3","answer":"aider","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"f2plnrx8i7ejgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"almoçar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"cp4yinljldajgmbp5i3","answer":"déjeuner","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"dtxi59lr4xjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"alugar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"8rqak0dot9djgmbp5i3","answer":"louer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"bt4n15tt23jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"andar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"yp04mmrxirjgmbp5i3","answer":"marcher","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"hr2xjlcp21jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"apagar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bn574pwnf9vjgmbp5i3","answer":"éteindre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"fbyb4uxxfsfjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"apanhar","detail":"train","answers":[{"id":"q4j92z3oeaqjgmbp5i3","answer":"attraper","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"twd995qun9jgmbp5i3","answer":"prendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"m4eveemocfcjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"apontar","detail":"du doigt","answers":[{"id":"qv0lvg5we6jgmbp5i3","answer":"pointer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"uaida9bsr5jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"aprender","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ymvlpzx34mpjgmbp5i3","answer":"apprendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1xtk8xa27kdjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"arrumar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"hgmjea9x2dsjgmbp5i3","answer":"arranger","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"j6s949515ijgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"assinar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"8z5mb833a3xjgmbp5i3","answer":"signer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"m5t13h7lgpbjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"atinger","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"jtwqus0w0dkjgmbp5i3","answer":"atteindre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"w5vg3ub97mijgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"atrasar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"pob1gn69tjjgmbp5i3","answer":"retarder","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"hporvzdta9kjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"atravessar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"quhny9e3p3fjgmbp5i3","answer":"traverser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"jv6vg7grw9qjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"beber","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"3gvxieklfvejgmbp5i3","answer":"boire","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"e6q7mh50izgjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"beija","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"oflzmqiqepjgmbp5i3","answer":"embrasser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"hjz9jaqnas4jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"brincar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"12jxi7zj2uyijgmbp5i3","answer":"jouer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"6qhbkjsc803jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"caminhar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"oxlzfj5dbgjgmbp5i3","answer":"marcher","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"qoco0sanbhpjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"cancelar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"7curijur5ljgmbp5i3","answer":"annuler","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"qy0wywvpz1ajgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"cantar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"53hbh4kymcjgmbp5i3","answer":"chanter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"fjp34u8d5ygjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"carregar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"30847r3036xjgmbp5i3","answer":"charger","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"pjwe215h50ajgmbp5i3","answer":"transporter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ya8q1cjvhv7jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"casar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"05ndwpptevpdjgmbp5i3","answer":"marier","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"a8vg5hn0u3jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"chamar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"rorhaj8r53jgmbp5i3","answer":"appeler","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"glqdtthwafjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"chegar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"gatobt4qs3bjgmbp5i3","answer":"arriver","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"67xen1yk7o8jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"chorar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"0eh0y99wgsbcjgmbp5i3","answer":"pleurer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"yrcjwhsmv8djgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"colocar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"6p5d2a0z7c8jgmbp5i3","answer":"mettre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"7iz7i0ebpdmjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"combinar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"kgb3n1lri4njgmbp5i3","answer":"combiner","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1ya49mf2ksbjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"começar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"zjos22rl3ogjgmbp5i3","answer":"commencer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"45nnbc3949ejgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"comer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"2pad0l8wj87jgmbp5i3","answer":"manger","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"mcpkt70ssljgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"comprar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"wmium7ucf9qjgmbp5i3","answer":"acheter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1mqb71s50ufjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"concordar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"l4bz4r2x3pkjgmbp5i3","answer":"être d'accord","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"lpy7lxn6l4tjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"conduzir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"x2n78eke8jejgmbp5i3","answer":"conduire","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"mgqx4560xjnjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"conhecer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"i5qbpsudnbjgmbp5i3","answer":"connaître","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"3lhtuckdlw6jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"continuar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"qqga5x2xrdjgmbp5i3","answer":"continuer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"u84tso7exx9jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"conversar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"gdt6wrbj6zhjgmbp5i3","answer":"converser","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"w5o3j0dx14fjgmbp5i3","answer":"discuter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"6vuwgjm9zu7jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"convidar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"l0ctm9h5lwjgmbp5i3","answer":"convier","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"ev0z8p90m4jgmbp5i3","answer":"inviter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"84320yritugjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"costumar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"mbsrvc352pmjgmbp5i3","answer":"avoir l'habitude de","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ycl41ct2tddjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"cozinhar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"m13ich6govpjgmbp5i3","answer":"cuisiner","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"mc9vabfo0kejgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"crescer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"uva2mdc3soejgmbp5i3","answer":"grandir","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"fnluokmh4njgmbp5i3","answer":"croitre","detail":"","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"foundType":"question","questionnaireTitle":"Palavras importantes ","questionnaireId":"di3ybmd51d8jgc7thdt","questionnaireType":"questionnaire"},{"id":"0i5pq4vnr8dtjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"cuidar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"liul7v6osqjgmbp5i3","answer":"s'occuper","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"jnvy4w9m3tljgmbp5i3","answer":"prendre soin","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"v24mojyjt6jgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"dançar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"hs3bw7bw8xajgmbp5i3","answer":"danser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"qqo1brnenijgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"deixar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"7glgxgr85rdjgmbp5i3","answer":"laisser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"maglbp6vuxmjgmbp5i3","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"descansar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"u9lg9cvjlmhjgmbp5i4","answer":"se reposer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ajcihkz6s7jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"descer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"qjwkhino3ocjgmbp5i4","answer":"descendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"7vootopuxe7jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"desejar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"sswz5kuhe7ojgmbp5i4","answer":"souhaiter","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"z5atjz6o2ejgmbp5i4","answer":"désirer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"0azk7yolk5anjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"desenhar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"x4hc3u3zb9djgmbp5i4","answer":"dessiner","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"c0ewedor23ujgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"desligar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"nbgs4k4so8ljgmbp5i4","answer":"déconnecter","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"n14kjp8vmcqjgmbp5i4","answer":"éteindre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"eltx70zx2itjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"encher","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"k2hn7qjz2bjgmbp5i4","answer":"remplir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"db347xlzforjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"encontrar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"7poh9a20ka3jgmbp5i4","answer":"trouver","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"5aq6uqbm5axjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"enganar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ouvwqb14yaojgmbp5i4","answer":"tromper","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"z5n7pof1h1qjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"entender","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bsf2yzgf3jajgmbp5i4","answer":"comprendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"y2q39ebklejgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"entrar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"0rb20svff0gejgmbp5i4","answer":"entrer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1e0yj5mm6ajjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"entregar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ukui83zpdjjjgmbp5i4","answer":"livrer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9i0wep6s7rwjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"enviar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"gq28fsrld7njgmbp5i4","answer":"envoyer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"guygrg5gp2kjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"errar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ejqin3ln22pjgmbp5i4","answer":"rater","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"ww6j5f9ai2pjgmbp5i4","answer":"faire une erreur","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ko30nw9y2jgjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"escolher","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"6v7to8h8ffnjgmbp5i4","answer":"choisir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"j8gze3x9onkjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"escrever","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"inastgetj9jgmbp5i4","answer":"écrire","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"g0mo6r1e1cjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"esperar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"gnialvmjtprjgmbp5i4","answer":"attendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"6wvkfdugximjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"esquecer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ypoonv5471bjgmbp5i4","answer":"oublier","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"vnes3umojlijgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"estudar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"389l5tgzhnejgmbp5i4","answer":"étudier","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"e7a9w73lvw5jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"explicar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"zqipg9t0s5jgmbp5i4","answer":"expliquer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"yoyzdmqmrrijgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"falar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"pkpzovpw887jgmbp5i4","answer":"parler","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"tjajmnkx08jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"falhar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"siay41zt7bjgmbp5i4","answer":"échouer","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"uecyheejbwljgmbp5i4","answer":"faillir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"yowcmvyxu5jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"fechar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"t2kln7tc5njgmbp5i4","answer":"fermer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"4sr5kfxoawrjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"ferver","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"r7hbgaocosjgmbp5i4","answer":"bouillir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"hncc0ts3l24jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"ficar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"6rg35tkzn5fjgmbp5i4","answer":"se trouver","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"eghzvw8irgjgmbp5i4","answer":"rester","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"l3uq6ddc03jjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"gostar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"2690gj0ph2ijgmbp5i4","answer":"aimer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ln1jztkldvdjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"guardar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"s383hqgsu0rjgmbp5i4","answer":"garder","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"dqx5351ngeqjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"jantar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"n81vvaz9bgbjgmbp5i4","answer":"diner","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"w12kectv34djgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"jogar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"jzwjzq3rddqjgmbp5i4","answer":"jouer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ih223733x4ejgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"julgar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"62s3clud4g2jgmbp5i4","answer":"juger","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"dva827j2n7ujgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"lavar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"qbjjyc0s9tjgmbp5i4","answer":"laver","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9g4yq36nk2gjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"levantar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"hz2j8zvdzvojgmbp5i4","answer":"lever","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"74gkhf6gu2ijgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"levar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"sua8vzrfs1gjgmbp5i4","answer":"prendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"a24820nd3rajgmbp5i4","answer":"amener","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"foundType":"question","questionnaireTitle":"Palavras importantes ","questionnaireId":"di3ybmd51d8jgc7thdt"},{"id":"411mgzmm6najgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"ligar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bhamky4ytjgmbp5i4","answer":"connecter","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"fvvcdbg95zdjgmbp5i4","answer":"appeler au téléphone","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"eddc0t6iulbjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"limpar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ocwefjai1xjgmbp5i4","answer":"nettoyer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"88zdb6d1xr6jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"machucar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"heivm5rcd2mjgmbp5i4","answer":"faire mal","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ygl723wx2wfjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"manter","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"0frdqqrzr0d9jgmbp5i4","answer":"garder","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"fae38rd3gnujgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"manter","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bq0wwv70c1ijgmbp5i4","answer":"garder","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"zojb1zz22sbjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"mergulhar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"h4djsce46vjgmbp5i4","answer":"plonger","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"5gviuxl3qjpjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"mexer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"n55a21diz5jgmbp5i4","answer":"déplacer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"j4f7c8ot1tkjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"molhar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"6xg93eiadnjgmbp5i4","answer":"mouiller","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"yh8tz42e8aajgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"morar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"cfxv889i57rjgmbp5i4","answer":"résider","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"fr213acsm7jjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"mudar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"vdhnumjtobjgmbp5i4","answer":"changer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"scc4n0xyiwdjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"nadar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"d3150louwfajgmbp5i4","answer":"nager","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"pcci16ikznpjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"necessitar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"2m47jjz2f1jgmbp5i4","answer":"nécessiter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"b5efit4k1s5jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"oferecer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ih26v4z77rnjgmbp5i4","answer":"offrir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"6k5bzikaav9jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"olhar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"i7cbhp4v3qjgmbp5i4","answer":"regarder","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"whh14ryc8qfjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"ouvir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"6c7gtyfsjbfjgmbp5i4","answer":"entendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"dfbewlctb84jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pagar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"zorp0rsxswjgmbp5i4","answer":"payer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1a2za1mu4ltjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"parar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"k1ii50g1ymjgmbp5i4","answer":"arrêter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ezsoep37wn4jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"partir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"giv9sm5jyj8jgmbp5i4","answer":"partir","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"wm8uuw5hzqfjgmbp5i4","answer":"casser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"1uw0whath0ljgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"passar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"3nzxq35n2dvjgmbp5i4","answer":"passer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"41a354rr3oujgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pedir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"wor3cum0q9jgmbp5i4","answer":"demander","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"ugll50dyiajgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pegar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"giyscukn4k8jgmbp5i4","answer":"attraper","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"wmpbfdi3w8jgmbp5i4","answer":"prendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9fzuuhcc6kijgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pensar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"0b7q5w7chevjgmbp5i4","answer":"penser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"d28j8cexwbojgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"perguntar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"g96l0ch2fcojgmbp5i4","answer":"demander","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"9iltzlnb2ghjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"pintar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"1klgdpqgv64jgmbp5i4","answer":"peindre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"38ngmkcjfpnjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"praticar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"28791blh2mmjgmbp5i4","answer":"pratiquer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"qisbpbdgsk7jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"precisar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"yh4u1lvdiljgmbp5i4","answer":"avoir besoin de","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"htwhg3z766njgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"querer","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"pjzry0usd7jgmbp5i4","answer":"vouloir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"af5b685akwojgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"receber","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"6nazz1fan4cjgmbp5i4","answer":"recevoir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"i15nsnj9a3jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"reservar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"q317q89a66kjgmbp5i4","answer":"réserver","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"xbzbw5qi8zjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"responder","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"d0hx8hywy6fjgmbp5i4","answer":"répondre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"65mnb5tvo8bjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"rir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"1z2ujr292nzjgmbp5i4","answer":"rire","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"kdlw2pmbrhrjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"soletrar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"dpyx11xhv7ajgmbp5i4","answer":"épeler","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"bsukb9t9rssjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"subir","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"uw0o22dotojgmbp5i4","answer":"monter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"tqb1jvgi28fjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"suceder","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"as1020mrrrjgmbp5i4","answer":"réussir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"670jjwayunfjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"telefonar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"10th1xbx1i7ojgmbp5i4","answer":"téléphoner","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"6dr0dcwo0uwjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"tentar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"q4wm5pk7jjjgmbp5i4","answer":"essayer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"lu655ft006jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"terminar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ygnxhn3d63jgmbp5i4","answer":"terminer","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"xs8s1l812jjgmbp5i4","answer":"finir","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"olljznfuf1jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"tocar","detail":"(instrument)","answers":[{"id":"y50af48qlqpjgmbp5i4","answer":"toucher","correctDistance":0,"point":1},{"id":"1cnta1agkl9jgmbp5i4","answer":"jouer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"xbwczdn228jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"tomar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"v2axn8wwe9jgmbp5i4","answer":"prendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"fzmsx066o4wjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"trabalhar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"3w3ah5g77ejgmbp5i4","answer":"travailler","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"kkm45roauqjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"trocar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"vg7ojz9plwdjgmbp5i4","answer":"échanger","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"5frx5gxkrnwjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"usar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"uuhvke7je3ljgmbp5i4","answer":"utiliser","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"f7y59gmdlhdjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"vender","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ziefyphpypnjgmbp5i4","answer":"vendre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"t9s5af0vk3pjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"viajar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"foyw5kj4jurjgmbp5i4","answer":"voyager","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"f9gorzx3x56jgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"virar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"c3dmb24ejm8jgmbp5i4","answer":"tourner","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"08ofpafaoxbdjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"visitar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"vbeubw6so2bjgmbp5i4","answer":"visiter","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"i3nnvbt86zkjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"viver","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"47rtjl3doytjgmbp5i4","answer":"vivre","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"xg1892uyo2jjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"voar","detail":"avion","answers":[{"id":"1oipm4dhzw5jgmbp5i4","answer":"voler","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"p8zbijkzivdjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"voltar","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"5k02g8kxy76jgmbp5i4","answer":"retourner","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1},{"id":"utyjccotcfjgmbp5i4","questionLabel":"Traduzir","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"treina","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"89did94g7p8jgmbp5i4","answer":"s'entrainer","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1}],"importQuestions":true,"fileName":"jxdyedyiskrjgmbp5i3.json","modificationDate":"2018-05-03 16:31:45","showGroup":false,"favoriteQuestions":false,"showQuestions":true}